{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821302891","data":{"timestamp":" 947821302891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821309077","data":{"timestamp":" 947821309076"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821317766","data":{"timestamp":" 947821317766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_5+1"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821333937","data":{"timestamp":" 947821333937"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_6+1"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821349348","data":{"timestamp":" 947821349348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_4+4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821361792","data":{"timestamp":" 947821361791"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" C"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821367692","data":{"timestamp":" 947821367692"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_2+6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821378092","data":{"timestamp":" 947821378092"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+0"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821387406","data":{"timestamp":" 947821387406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_8+0"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821396592","data":{"timestamp":" 947821396592"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821403566","data":{"timestamp":" 947821403565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+3"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821415763","data":{"timestamp":" 947821415763"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_0+5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821434794","data":{"timestamp":" 947821434794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821446424","data":{"timestamp":" 947821446424"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821456405","data":{"timestamp":" 947821456405"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821465806","data":{"timestamp":" 947821465805"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821473037","data":{"timestamp":" 947821473036"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7730bb92-0b60-4c54-93df-3466e620e6c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.arith_ADD-1D-H.1__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_3+2"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821490913","data":{"timestamp":" 947821490913"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_saba"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821508230","data":{"timestamp":" 947821508230"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821509835","data":{"timestamp":" 947821509835"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821519964","data":{"timestamp":" 947821519964"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821528999","data":{"timestamp":" 947821528999"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821533093","data":{"timestamp":" 947821533093"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821543891","data":{"timestamp":" 947821543891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821554818","data":{"timestamp":" 947821554818"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821561767","data":{"timestamp":" 947821561767"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_vye"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821576495","data":{"timestamp":" 947821576495"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821579562","data":{"timestamp":" 947821579562"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821589925","data":{"timestamp":" 947821589925"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821591276","data":{"timestamp":" 947821591276"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_shi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821612811","data":{"timestamp":" 947821612811"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821627086","data":{"timestamp":" 947821627086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821637278","data":{"timestamp":" 947821637278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" x"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821647017","data":{"timestamp":" 947821647017"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821650184","data":{"timestamp":" 947821650184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821651515","data":{"timestamp":" 947821651515"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nyo"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821678298","data":{"timestamp":" 947821678298"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_she"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821680039","data":{"timestamp":" 947821680039"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_she"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821682840","data":{"timestamp":" 947821682840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_she"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821693740","data":{"timestamp":" 947821693740"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_she"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821694363","data":{"timestamp":" 947821694363"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_she"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821698224","data":{"timestamp":" 947821698224"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_she"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821712891","data":{"timestamp":" 947821712891"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821724320","data":{"timestamp":" 947821724320"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821724633","data":{"timestamp":" 947821724633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821727115","data":{"timestamp":" 947821727115"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821743082","data":{"timestamp":" 947821743082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821744941","data":{"timestamp":" 947821744941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821761463","data":{"timestamp":" 947821761462"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821765391","data":{"timestamp":" 947821765391"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd.dic:syl.3ch..3ch..10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821775291","data":{"timestamp":" 947821775291"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 19f6defa-6c0d-4010-a8c6-ff8b9555dcde"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd.dic_syl.3ch..3ch..10"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_nge"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821791445","data":{"timestamp":" 947821791444"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821791671","data":{"timestamp":" 947821791671"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821792634","data":{"timestamp":" 947821792634"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821793931","data":{"timestamp":" 947821793931"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821806626","data":{"timestamp":" 947821806626"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821807474","data":{"timestamp":" 947821807474"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821807788","data":{"timestamp":" 947821807787"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821809021","data":{"timestamp":" 947821809021"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821813179","data":{"timestamp":" 947821813179"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821814164","data":{"timestamp":" 947821814163"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821814419","data":{"timestamp":" 947821814419"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821815362","data":{"timestamp":" 947821815362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821818227","data":{"timestamp":" 947821818227"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821819264","data":{"timestamp":" 947821819264"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821819737","data":{"timestamp":" 947821819737"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821824291","data":{"timestamp":" 947821824290"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821824455","data":{"timestamp":" 947821824455"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 1f62fa72-131c-4e21-908d-3d46dd660b5c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821845597","data":{"timestamp":" 947821845597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bwa_ndi-msa-bwa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bwa"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821869390","data":{"timestamp":" 947821869390"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nge_vya-nge-dha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nge"," userResponse":" vya"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821876236","data":{"timestamp":" 947821876236"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nge_vya-nge-dha"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nge"," userResponse":" nge"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821888892","data":{"timestamp":" 947821888892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mki_bwa-mki-mpe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mki"," userResponse":" mki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821919275","data":{"timestamp":" 947821919275"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwi_mwi-ngi-mzu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwi"," userResponse":" mzu"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821926477","data":{"timestamp":" 947821926477"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwi_mwi-ngi-mzu"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwi"," userResponse":" mwi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821932402","data":{"timestamp":" 947821932402"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_ndo-nda-she"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" ndo"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821938533","data":{"timestamp":" 947821938533"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_she_ndo-nda-she"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" she"," userResponse":" she"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821945510","data":{"timestamp":" 947821945510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_sho_mgu-sho-nji"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" sho"," userResponse":" sho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821950979","data":{"timestamp":" 947821950979"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_twe_nja-dha-twe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" twe"," userResponse":" twe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821955668","data":{"timestamp":" 947821955667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_kha-mna-bwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" bwa"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821961949","data":{"timestamp":" 947821961948"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mna_kha-mna-bwa"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mna"," userResponse":" mna"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821967285","data":{"timestamp":" 947821967285"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbu_kha-mbu-twe"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821971609","data":{"timestamp":" 947821971609"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_mzi-nji-mre"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nji"," userResponse":" nji"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821977412","data":{"timestamp":" 947821977412"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_mzi-nji-mre"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:2..12.off1.2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947821986170","data":{"timestamp":" 947821986170"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" f36d7209-d529-4f8c-9394-6c3d7645240f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_nji_mzi-nji-mre"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822002892","data":{"timestamp":" 947822002892"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 56f7279e-540e-4e62-b009-c83e9038faaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbu_kha-mbu-twe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" kha"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822020872","data":{"timestamp":" 947822020872"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 56f7279e-540e-4e62-b009-c83e9038faaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mbu_kha-mbu-twe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbu"," userResponse":" mbu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822022987","data":{"timestamp":" 947822022987"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 56f7279e-540e-4e62-b009-c83e9038faaf"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_3ch..3ch.syl.rand.all.stat.noShow.78"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mbu_kha-mbu-twe"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822032057","data":{"timestamp":" 947822032057"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822032281","data":{"timestamp":" 947822032280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822033274","data":{"timestamp":" 947822033274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822034548","data":{"timestamp":" 947822034548"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822037436","data":{"timestamp":" 947822037436"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822038281","data":{"timestamp":" 947822038280"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822038595","data":{"timestamp":" 947822038595"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822039860","data":{"timestamp":" 947822039859"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SERENGETI"," userResponse":" SERENGETI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822043334","data":{"timestamp":" 947822043334"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGORONGORO"," userResponse":" NGORONGORO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822044318","data":{"timestamp":" 947822044318"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYARA"," userResponse":" MANYARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822044572","data":{"timestamp":" 947822044572"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822045516","data":{"timestamp":" 947822045516"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ngorongoro Manyara na Mikumi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIKUMI"," userResponse":" MIKUMI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822048356","data":{"timestamp":" 947822048355"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822049389","data":{"timestamp":" 947822049389"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822049861","data":{"timestamp":" 947822049861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822054407","data":{"timestamp":" 947822054406"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822054624","data":{"timestamp":" 947822054624"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7b5e0288-cc22-4f7f-bcf7-a6e8545504ca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O Tanzania oyee!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OYEE"," userResponse":" OYEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822070314","data":{"timestamp":" 947822070314"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 917158f2-6690-4ac0-817f-fc088336ab01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haja_watu-haja-zizi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haja"," userResponse":" haja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822079051","data":{"timestamp":" 947822079051"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 917158f2-6690-4ac0-817f-fc088336ab01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_wale-ombe-hana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822081943","data":{"timestamp":" 947822081941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 917158f2-6690-4ac0-817f-fc088336ab01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_wale-ombe-hana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822100359","data":{"timestamp":" 947822100359"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 917158f2-6690-4ac0-817f-fc088336ab01"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_wale-ombe-hana"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822118231","data":{"timestamp":" 947822118231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822118647","data":{"timestamp":" 947822118647"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822121658","data":{"timestamp":" 947822121658"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822123172","data":{"timestamp":" 947822123172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822125024","data":{"timestamp":" 947822125024"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822125460","data":{"timestamp":" 947822125460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822125966","data":{"timestamp":" 947822125966"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822126613","data":{"timestamp":" 947822126613"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Upinde una rangi saba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822129360","data":{"timestamp":" 947822129360"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822131022","data":{"timestamp":" 947822131022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822134800","data":{"timestamp":" 947822134800"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822137259","data":{"timestamp":" 947822137259"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822145151","data":{"timestamp":" 947822145151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822147510","data":{"timestamp":" 947822147510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822149367","data":{"timestamp":" 947822149366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822149460","data":{"timestamp":" 947822149460"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822150315","data":{"timestamp":" 947822150315"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822150731","data":{"timestamp":" 947822150731"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822151559","data":{"timestamp":" 947822151558"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya kwanza ni nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822155759","data":{"timestamp":" 947822155759"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" START_KWEYU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822157103","data":{"timestamp":" 947822157103"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822158231","data":{"timestamp":" 947822158231"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822160009","data":{"timestamp":" 947822160009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822160793","data":{"timestamp":" 947822160793"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822161204","data":{"timestamp":" 947822161204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" START_RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822163547","data":{"timestamp":" 947822163547"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822168174","data":{"timestamp":" 947822168173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822169982","data":{"timestamp":" 947822169982"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWEYU"," userResponse":" KWEYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822171027","data":{"timestamp":" 947822171027"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEVALIA"," userResponse":" AMEVALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822171721","data":{"timestamp":" 947822171720"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHATI"," userResponse":" SHATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822171916","data":{"timestamp":" 947822171916"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822172491","data":{"timestamp":" 947822172491"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822173287","data":{"timestamp":" 947822173287"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kweyu amevalia shati la rangi nyekundu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYEKUNDU"," userResponse":" NYEKUNDU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822176858","data":{"timestamp":" 947822176858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822177952","data":{"timestamp":" 947822177952"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822178144","data":{"timestamp":" 947822178144"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822178552","data":{"timestamp":" 947822178552"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822178850","data":{"timestamp":" 947822178850"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822179366","data":{"timestamp":" 947822179366"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822179393","data":{"timestamp":" 947822179393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" START_CHUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822182856","data":{"timestamp":" 947822182856"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822184659","data":{"timestamp":" 947822184659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822184764","data":{"timestamp":" 947822184764"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822185528","data":{"timestamp":" 947822185528"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PILI"," userResponse":" PILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822186044","data":{"timestamp":" 947822186044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822186238","data":{"timestamp":" 947822186238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822186912","data":{"timestamp":" 947822186912"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya pili ni ya chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822192598","data":{"timestamp":" 947822192598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" START_HILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822193782","data":{"timestamp":" 947822193782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822195270","data":{"timestamp":" 947822195269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822196846","data":{"timestamp":" 947822196846"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822201593","data":{"timestamp":" 947822201593"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822203060","data":{"timestamp":" 947822203060"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822208161","data":{"timestamp":" 947822208161"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822209789","data":{"timestamp":" 947822209789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILI"," userResponse":" HILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822210015","data":{"timestamp":" 947822210015"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822210722","data":{"timestamp":" 947822210722"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hili ni chungwa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUNGWA"," userResponse":" CHUNGWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822215340","data":{"timestamp":" 947822215339"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822215351","data":{"timestamp":" 947822215350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822217557","data":{"timestamp":" 947822217556"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822217565","data":{"timestamp":" 947822217565"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822217644","data":{"timestamp":" 947822217644"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822219445","data":{"timestamp":" 947822219445"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822219562","data":{"timestamp":" 947822219561"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822220266","data":{"timestamp":" 947822220266"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822220755","data":{"timestamp":" 947822220755"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822221569","data":{"timestamp":" 947822221569"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tatu ni manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822224840","data":{"timestamp":" 947822224840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822226977","data":{"timestamp":" 947822226977"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822227769","data":{"timestamp":" 947822227769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822229265","data":{"timestamp":" 947822229265"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822230250","data":{"timestamp":" 947822230250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822232073","data":{"timestamp":" 947822232073"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822232077","data":{"timestamp":" 947822232077"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822233058","data":{"timestamp":" 947822233058"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822233086","data":{"timestamp":" 947822233086"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822234983","data":{"timestamp":" 947822234983"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822235621","data":{"timestamp":" 947822235620"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PINGU"," userResponse":" PINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822236355","data":{"timestamp":" 947822236354"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LINA"," userResponse":" LINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822237070","data":{"timestamp":" 947822237070"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822237209","data":{"timestamp":" 947822237208"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822238053","data":{"timestamp":" 947822238053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai pingu lina rangi ya manjano."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANJANO"," userResponse":" MANJANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822242408","data":{"timestamp":" 947822242408"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822242768","data":{"timestamp":" 947822242768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822243123","data":{"timestamp":" 947822243123"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822243582","data":{"timestamp":" 947822243582"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822244526","data":{"timestamp":" 947822244526"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822246275","data":{"timestamp":" 947822246274"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822246420","data":{"timestamp":" 947822246420"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822247143","data":{"timestamp":" 947822247143"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NNE"," userResponse":" NNE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822247659","data":{"timestamp":" 947822247659"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822248400","data":{"timestamp":" 947822248400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya nne ni kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822254238","data":{"timestamp":" 947822254238"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822254605","data":{"timestamp":" 947822254604"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822255840","data":{"timestamp":" 947822255840"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822256310","data":{"timestamp":" 947822256309"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822257044","data":{"timestamp":" 947822257044"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822258980","data":{"timestamp":" 947822258980"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MIWA"," userResponse":" MIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822259414","data":{"timestamp":" 947822259414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822259909","data":{"timestamp":" 947822259909"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822260034","data":{"timestamp":" 947822260033"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822260789","data":{"timestamp":" 947822260789"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Miwa ni rangi ya kijani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIJANI"," userResponse":" KIJANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822265438","data":{"timestamp":" 947822265437"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" START_RANGI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822266579","data":{"timestamp":" 947822266579"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822266786","data":{"timestamp":" 947822266786"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822267181","data":{"timestamp":" 947822267180"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822267794","data":{"timestamp":" 947822267794"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822268501","data":{"timestamp":" 947822268501"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" START_SAMAWATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822269529","data":{"timestamp":" 947822269529"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" START_SAMAWATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822271685","data":{"timestamp":" 947822271685"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822273439","data":{"timestamp":" 947822273438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822273554","data":{"timestamp":" 947822273554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822274308","data":{"timestamp":" 947822274308"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANO"," userResponse":" TANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822274682","data":{"timestamp":" 947822274682"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822275766","data":{"timestamp":" 947822275766"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya tano ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822280072","data":{"timestamp":" 947822280072"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822281232","data":{"timestamp":" 947822281232"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822281372","data":{"timestamp":" 947822281372"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" START_SAMAWATI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822282597","data":{"timestamp":" 947822282597"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822284706","data":{"timestamp":" 947822284706"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822286398","data":{"timestamp":" 947822286398"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBINGU"," userResponse":" MBINGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822286871","data":{"timestamp":" 947822286871"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822287876","data":{"timestamp":" 947822287876"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbingu ni samawati."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAWATI"," userResponse":" SAMAWATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822292732","data":{"timestamp":" 947822292732"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822293132","data":{"timestamp":" 947822293132"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822293137","data":{"timestamp":" 947822293136"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822293834","data":{"timestamp":" 947822293834"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822295527","data":{"timestamp":" 947822295527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822297273","data":{"timestamp":" 947822297273"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822297410","data":{"timestamp":" 947822297410"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822297985","data":{"timestamp":" 947822297985"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SITA"," userResponse":" SITA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822298250","data":{"timestamp":" 947822298250"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822298869","data":{"timestamp":" 947822298869"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya sita ni nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822303377","data":{"timestamp":" 947822303376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822303858","data":{"timestamp":" 947822303858"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822304864","data":{"timestamp":" 947822304863"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822305861","data":{"timestamp":" 947822305861"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822306091","data":{"timestamp":" 947822306091"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822306172","data":{"timestamp":" 947822306172"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822309370","data":{"timestamp":" 947822309370"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822311330","data":{"timestamp":" 947822311330"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MATUNDA"," userResponse":" MATUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822312051","data":{"timestamp":" 947822312050"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822312585","data":{"timestamp":" 947822312585"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822312743","data":{"timestamp":" 947822312743"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822313278","data":{"timestamp":" 947822313278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822313414","data":{"timestamp":" 947822313414"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822314011","data":{"timestamp":" 947822314011"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Matunda haya ni ya rangi ya nili."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NILI"," userResponse":" NILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822318393","data":{"timestamp":" 947822318393"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822320668","data":{"timestamp":" 947822320668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822321054","data":{"timestamp":" 947822321053"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" START_SABA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822322724","data":{"timestamp":" 947822322723"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822323768","data":{"timestamp":" 947822323768"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822324729","data":{"timestamp":" 947822324729"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" START_ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822327774","data":{"timestamp":" 947822327774"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822329198","data":{"timestamp":" 947822329198"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822330476","data":{"timestamp":" 947822330476"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822338322","data":{"timestamp":" 947822338322"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822340126","data":{"timestamp":" 947822340126"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822340221","data":{"timestamp":" 947822340220"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822340943","data":{"timestamp":" 947822340941"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822341377","data":{"timestamp":" 947822341377"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822342349","data":{"timestamp":" 947822342349"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rangi ya saba ni zambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" ZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822346465","data":{"timestamp":" 947822346465"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822347539","data":{"timestamp":" 947822347539"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822347549","data":{"timestamp":" 947822347549"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822348837","data":{"timestamp":" 947822348837"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822348924","data":{"timestamp":" 947822348924"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" START_KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822350310","data":{"timestamp":" 947822350310"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822352186","data":{"timestamp":" 947822352186"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822352461","data":{"timestamp":" 947822352461"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822353943","data":{"timestamp":" 947822353943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NGUO"," userResponse":" NGUO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822354207","data":{"timestamp":" 947822354206"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822354278","data":{"timestamp":" 947822354278"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822354350","data":{"timestamp":" 947822354350"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822354936","data":{"timestamp":" 947822354936"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nguo yangu ni ya kizambarau."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIZAMBARAU"," userResponse":" KIZAMBARAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822360323","data":{"timestamp":" 947822360323"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822361293","data":{"timestamp":" 947822361293"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822361483","data":{"timestamp":" 947822361482"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822365084","data":{"timestamp":" 947822365084"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822368770","data":{"timestamp":" 947822368769"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" START_NIIPENDAYO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822370671","data":{"timestamp":" 947822370670"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822372802","data":{"timestamp":" 947822372801"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822374317","data":{"timestamp":" 947822374316"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822374782","data":{"timestamp":" 947822374782"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822376357","data":{"timestamp":" 947822376357"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIIPENDAYO"," userResponse":" NIIPENDAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822377494","data":{"timestamp":" 947822377494"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ni rangi niipendayo zaidi!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822381594","data":{"timestamp":" 947822381594"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822382400","data":{"timestamp":" 947822382400"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" START_UNAZIJUA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822384550","data":{"timestamp":" 947822384550"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822396688","data":{"timestamp":" 947822396688"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822398426","data":{"timestamp":" 947822398426"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822400030","data":{"timestamp":" 947822400030"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822401879","data":{"timestamp":" 947822401879"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822403589","data":{"timestamp":" 947822403589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822405277","data":{"timestamp":" 947822405277"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JE"," userResponse":" JE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822407022","data":{"timestamp":" 947822407022"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNAZIJUA"," userResponse":" UNAZIJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822407496","data":{"timestamp":" 947822407496"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RANGI"," userResponse":" RANGI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822408083","data":{"timestamp":" 947822408082"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABA"," userResponse":" SABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822408380","data":{"timestamp":" 947822408379"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822409395","data":{"timestamp":" 947822409395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822412173","data":{"timestamp":" 947822412173"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822412633","data":{"timestamp":" 947822412633"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPINDE"," userResponse":" UPINDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822422184","data":{"timestamp":" 947822422184"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822429004","data":{"timestamp":" 947822429003"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822438822","data":{"timestamp":" 947822438822"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822446269","data":{"timestamp":" 947822446269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.arith:ADD-1D-H.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822459352","data":{"timestamp":" 947822459352"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 30b3bbe3-50a6-4b46-a35e-b9f02f3350e5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Je unazijua rangi saba za upinde?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822481283","data":{"timestamp":" 947822481282"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hasira_hasira_hakika_hawana"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822488006","data":{"timestamp":" 947822488006"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hajui_hayo_hajui_hatua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822495667","data":{"timestamp":" 947822495667"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hajui_hayo_hajui_hatua"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822502438","data":{"timestamp":" 947822502438"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hakuweza_hakujali_hakupata_hakuweza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822510151","data":{"timestamp":" 947822510151"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hakuweza_hakujali_hakupata_hakuweza"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822516928","data":{"timestamp":" 947822516928"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hawakuweza_hayo_hawezi_hawakuweza"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822523649","data":{"timestamp":" 947822523649"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hamu_hamu_harufu_hakupata"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822531306","data":{"timestamp":" 947822531305"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hamu_hamu_harufu_hakupata"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822538004","data":{"timestamp":" 947822538004"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hawana_hapo_hawakujua"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822545700","data":{"timestamp":" 947822545700"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_hawana_hapo_hawakujua"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822552471","data":{"timestamp":" 947822552471"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hawakuweza_hawakuweza_haraka_hakujua"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822559192","data":{"timestamp":" 947822559191"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hamu_harufu_hamu_hana"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822565938","data":{"timestamp":" 947822565938"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hata_haha_halikuwa_hata"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822573606","data":{"timestamp":" 947822573606"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" hata_haha_halikuwa_hata"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:begin.wrd.ha.show.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947822582668","data":{"timestamp":" 947822582668"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000114_064118"," gameId":" 7c4bb0c1-5b80-40d1-80e8-8fecd71ac74d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_begin.wrd.ha.show.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hata_haha_halikuwa_hata"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}